Moehammad Fazle Mawla Sidiki

Jl. Jeruk IIID, Sidoarjo, East Java / fazlesidiki@gmail.com / +62 851 5698 6534

Summary

Recent graduates from SMAN 15 Surabaya with an average Graduation Examination score of 91.51. Experienced in many organizational events. Have a dream to become an IT engineer in a large company in the automotive sector for fourwheeled vehicles or oil and gas, also has a strong interest in the field of energy sources, especially oil and gas. Having strong IT business acumen, the ability to manage time and work under pressure in dynamic conditions as a team, also flexible communication skills to adapt to rapid stakeholders, and a willingness to learn continuously, I believe I have the potential to be an asset value in a team.

Education

Senior Highschool Education

SMA Negeri 15 Surabaya, Surabaya, East Java 07/2022 Graduated with an average Graduation Exam score of 91.51.

Information System

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember , Surabaya, East Java Class 2022

Experience

Pemandu FTEIC ITS

Instructor, Surabaya, Jawa Timur 12/2023 - Present

'Pemandu FTEIC' is a community under the supervision of the ITS Guidance Coordination Body, consisting of a group of FT-EIC students tasked with serving as mentors and facilitators during the Student Management Skills Training event organized by the university. Here, I serve as a guide for the 'Beyondics' cohort, currently assigned to act as a facilitator and presenter in the upcoming Pre-TD IV FT-EIC event.

SPE ITS SC

Staff Research and Information, Surabaya, East Java 08/2023 - Present

The Society of Petroleum Engineers (SPE) is a not-for-profit professional association whose more than 153,646 members in 145 countries are engaged in oil and gas exploration and production. SPE is a key resource for technical knowledge providing opportunities to exchange information at in-person and online events and training courses, publications, and other resources.

Becoming a staff of the Research & Information division in SPE ITS SC 23/24, took me to a higher level of organizational ability because of some of my responsibility to enrich the understanding of the energy industry among SPE ITS SC's members, boards, and compliance delegates using online platforms, multimedia, books, articles, and online publications. Additionally, organizing training programs to enhance the technical skills of the members.

MABA CUP ITS 2023 by LMB ITS

Head of Public Relations, Surabaya, East Java 08/2023 - 02/2024

Maba Cup is an annual event held for new students by LMB ITS which consists of managerial training and various competitions. In this event, I have the following tasks and achievements during my position as Head of the public relations division at Maba Cup 2023:

- 1. Establish media cooperation with several HMD and BEM-F, also BEM-ITS to promote the event.
- 2. Contacting and inviting several representatives and important parties related to the event.
- 3. Become a leader means giving instruction, controlling, advising, and leading the staff of the Public Relations division related to their job desk
- 4. Responsible for anything related to this division

PARADIGM ISE! 2023

Staff of Intermediary Subdivision, Surabaya, East Java 04/2023 - 10/2023

ISE! 2023 is the largest annual event organized by the Information Systems Department of the Surabaya Sepuluh Nopember Institute of Technology with the aim of introducing the name of the ITS Information Systems Department to a wider audience. There are 4 sub-events in ISE!, these are BIONIX, ICON, RISE, & PARADIGM. Here I have a role as staff of the PARADIGM - INTERM sub-program which has the following tasks:

- 1. Building Relationships with Musicians, MCs, Talents, and various other types of performers.
- 2. Negotiate & Establish contracts and cooperation with the performers.
- 3. Being LO for the performers.

GERIGI ITS 2023

Secretarial Subdivision Expert Staff, Surabaya, East Java 07/2023 - 08/2023

GERIGI ITS 2023 is one of the biggest events at ITS where, GERIGI is an activity to welcome new ITS students. By becoming an expert staff member of the secretarial subdivision, data management division, I have the following roles:

- 1. Assist & provide direction to secretarial staff while on duty at GERIGI ITS 2023
- 2. Being the contact person, and responsible for the secretarial staff for Region 1 (supervising 10 staff, and in the 10 staff there are 20 staff each)
- 3. Assist in collecting and managing all the data needs of new students during the event

Iris Robotic Competition 2023

Liaison Officer, Surabaya, East Java 02/2023 - 08/2023

This year 2023, the IRIS ITS team has announced for the first time the first annual biggest event, namely IRC (IRIS Robotic Course and Competition). It is a national-scale robotics competition facilitated by robotics training sessions held by the ITS IRIS Robotics Team. This competition is intended for school students and is held in a hybrid manner (Online and Offline). Here I have a responsibility as a staff liaison officer who has the following tasks:

- 1. Contact and cooperate in event promotion with schools that have the potential to take part in the event.
- 2. Conduct promotional roadshow events
- 3. Directing, guiding, and being responsible for escorting the contestants' teams from the beginning to the end of the event.

PETROLIDA 2023

Petroleum Integrated Days (PETROLIDA) is the largest annual event held by the SPE ITS Student Chapter and will be the 11th event this year, 2023. Petrolida aims to be a forum for students to explore and innovate about current energy challenges by providing them the opportunity to gain substantial and competitive experience to further their advantage, as well as non-competitive experience. At PETROLIDA, I was given the responsibility of being the LO for the contestants which included guiding, directing, escorting, and providing support & encouragement to the contestants from the start to the end of the event.

ITS EXPO 2023

Data Management, Surabaya, East Java 01/2023 - 06/2023

ITS EXPO is an annual event held by Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember (ITS) Surabaya that exhibits artworks and technological innovations of ITS Students to be shown to the public. In this event, I have the following tasks:

- Responsible for all mechanisms and administrative procedures for the entire series of events
- Collect, store, and manage all data in organizational activities.
- Create and plan database processing arrangements and control and manage all event form data.

MABA CUP ITS 2022 by LMB ITS

Public Relations Officer, Surabaya, East Java

09/2022 - 12/2022

Maba Cup is an annual event held for new students by LMB ITS which consists of managerial training and various competitions. In this event, I have the following tasks and achievements:

- Establish media cooperation with several HMD and BEM-F at ITS to promote the event.
- Contacting and inviting several representatives and important parties related to the event.
- Become a liaison for the Competition Jury and several other external parties related to the event.

ANOMALI Magazine Vol.3 by OSIS/MPK SMAN 15 SURABAYA

Deputy Chief Editor, Surabaya, East Java

04/2021 - 01/2022

Anomali is an annual School Magazine organized by Commission C, MPK SMAN 15 SURABAYA which serves as a forum for students to channel their aspirations and creativity. Here are some of my obligations and achievements during my tenure:

- Responsible on supervised, directed, provided advice and solutions during the production.
- Determine the concept theme and created a new invention of 'Anomali Explore' that Anomali edition which is packaged in the form of a website with lots of surprising and varied popup content.

LIBELS CUP 2021 By OSIS/MPK SMAN 15 SURABAYA

Staff of Graphic Design Division, Surabaya, East Java 03/2021 - 07/2021

Libels Cup is an annual competition held by OSIS/MPK SMAN 15 SURABAYA that held online in 2021. As a staff of the graphic design division, here are some of my roles and achievements in the team:

- Create design templates for Instagram Story content purposes.
- Make creative proposal designs to be submitted to sponsors or media partners.

LEO x LIMIT 2021 By OSIS/MPK SMAN 15 SURABAYA

Staff of Graphic Design Division, Surabaya, East Java

12/2020 - 03/2021

LEO x LIMIT is an international-scale English language olympiad and several other disciplines, informative seminars inviting prestigious speakers. The event held online with an offline final round in 2021. During the event, I have the following responsibilities:

- · Create design for Instagram filters using AR Spark.
- Create design templates for Instagram Story content purposes.
- Make creative proposal designs to be submitted to sponsors or media partners.

OSIS/MPK SMAN 15 Surabaya 2020/2021

Deputy Chairman of Commission C, Surabaya, East Java 12/2019 - 01/2021

As Deputy Chair of Commission C from MPK SMAN 15 Surabaya 2020/2021, I have responsibilities including:

- Assist in carrying out the duties of the Chairman of the Commission.
- Processed suggestions, input, and aspirations from all school members.
- Realizing suggestions, inputs, and aspirations received through various commission work programs.
- Publishing ANOMALI Magazine.
- Initiated regular APK forums, a place where all representatives from every school community could discuss the problems that exist in the school environment and find solutions.

LIBELS DAY 2020 By OSIS/MPK SMAN 15 SURABAYA

Head of Division, Surabaya, East Java

08/2020 - 09/2020

Libels Day 2020 is an annual event organized by OSIS/MPK SMAN 15 Surabaya which aims to commemorate the birthday of SMAN 15 Surabaya. In this event, I have a role as chairman of the Libelsian 2020 competition division for Libelsian Boys and Girls 2020. In detail, my main tasks are:

- Designing the concept of this competition which will be executed online.
- Arranged tasks for 5 members.
- Supervised the work of 5 members.
- Processed input from students of SMAN 15 Surabaya regarding this competition.

LEO x LIMIT 2020 By OSIS/MPK SMAN 15 SURABAYA

Staff of Health and Consumption Division, Surabaya, East Java 01/2020 - 03/2020

LEO x LIMIT is an international-scale English language olympiad and several other disciplines, informative seminars by inviting prestigious speakers. The event is held fully offline. During the event, I have the following responsibilities:

- Fully responsible for providing food for the committee, participants, judges, and speakers during the event.
- Successfully collaborated with a well-known bakery brand as a supplier of snacks during the event at a friendly price.

LIBERTY 2019 By OSIS/MPK SMAN 15 SURABAYA

HR/HC Officer, Surabaya, East Java

08/2019 - 11/2019

LIBERTY 2019 is an annual art performance event organized by OSIS/MPK SMAN 15 Surabaya in 2019. LIBERTY is an event where students can show their talents and abilities, and the highlight of this event is a music concert involving several famous artists such as Reality Club, Kahitna, and Didi Kempot. As a member of the HR/HC Division, I handled:

- Supervised the event and the performance of the committee.
- Listening to complaints related to events.
- Improve the performance of the committee.
- Provide solutions to problems that exist in the event.

Course & License

RevoU Mini Course Data Analytics: Introduction to Data Analytics, Basic Phyton, Google Data Studio. (2023)

ITS Basic Level Entrepreneurship Student Skills Training (LKMW-TD) (2022)

ITS Basic Level Scientific Writing Training (PKTI - TD) (2022)

ITS Basic & Advanced Media Schooling (BMS - AMS) (2023)

ITS Student Management Skills Training (LKMM-Pre TD & LKMM-TD) (2023)

ITS Instructor Training of Student Management Skills Training (LKMM-PP) (2023)

Sales & Business Development - Pitching, Negoitation, & Closing, MySkill Short Course (2024)

Data Analyst - Data Visualization Practice, MySkill Short Course (2024)

Honorary Awards

Youth Leader MUN (Model United Nations) 2021

Delegates of WHO from Thailand, Online Conference, 01/2021

Youth Leader MUN 2021 is a debate competition based on Model United Nations organized by Non-Governmental Organizations (NGOs). As a representative of the WHO and a delegation from Thailand in discussing the issue of the Covid-19 Pandemic. Here are some of my roles and achievements during the event:

- Be a representative of Thailand.
- Raise and discuss issues and problems related to the Covid-19 Pandemic in Thailand with their solutions.
- Provide critical thinking on the problems of the Covid-19 Pandemic in the world.
- Express some suggestions and solutions to problems related to the Covid-19 Pandemic in several countries.

Skills

Microsoft Office, Google Sites, Social Media Monitoring, Leadership Experience, Public Speaking, Adaptability, Spreadsheets, WordPress

Languages

English, Indonesian

Social Media

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/fazlesidiki

Instagram: instagram.com/mfazms

GitHub: github.com/mfazms

Portofolio Instagram: instagram.com/azecorp